Ginny & Georgia - The Afterparty is a documentary film directed by Joe Guidry.
Cast members of the hit Netflix show join the hosts to unpack the drama of Season
1, and Cristela Alonzo offers tips for being the new kid at school.
Self - Host, played by David Spade.
Self - Host, played by London Hughes.
Self - Host, played by Fortune Feimster.
Self, played by Brianne Howey.
Self, played by Antonia Gentry.
Self, played by Jennifer Robertson.
Ginny & Georgia is an American comedy-drama
television series created by Sarah Lampert.
It premiered on Netflix on February 24, 2021, and follows the life of thirty‑one‑year‑old Georgia Miller (portrayed by Brianne Howey) and her teenage
children, Ginny (Antonia Gentry) and Austin (Diesel La Torraca), as they relocate to the fictional town of Wellsbury, Massachusetts.
The show blends elements of teen drama, family
dynamics, mystery, and darker themes.
Upon its debut, Ginny & Georgia drew comparisons to Gilmore Girls for its quick-witted mother-daughter
dynamic but carved its own path with a blend of heartfelt family scenes and dramatic turns.
In April 2021, the series was renewed for a second
season, which premiered on January 5, 2023.
In May 2023, the series was renewed for a third and fourth season.
The third season premiered on June 5, 2025.
There were 52 million subscribers who watched the first season of
the series for the first 28 days after its release.
It has also prompted widespread discussion on themes like identity,
mental health, family secrets, and moral ambiguity.
The casting drew attention after season 3, with media noting
several teen actors were older than their characters.